Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1968-2004; Undated; 3; 11.4 cu. ft.
  - Steel - Newsclippings, 1991; 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Steel, Pennsylvania, 1996-1998 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - STORET Groundwater - Data and Correspondence, 1988; 1997; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Stormwater, 1992-1994; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14-16)
  - Superfund Cleanup Standards and National Priorities List Sites, 1986-1987 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Supplemental Projects and General Settlements, 1991; 1994-1995 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Survey of the Nation's Toxic Polluters, 1991 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Testimony, "EPA's" Penalties May Not Recover Economic Benefits Gained by Violators", 1991 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Toxic Chemical Release Inventory Summary Report for Michigan, 1989 Data, 1991 October (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - The Toxic-Free Diet, 1997 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Toxic Release Inventory, State Program Assessment, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Toxics Release Inventory, 1991; 1994-1995 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - Trash Incinerators, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Tug Hill - Correspondence, Summary and Reports, 1973-1976; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Ultrox UV/Oxidation Systems, Summary and Pamphlets, 1989; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - United Steelworkers of America Materials About Landis Plastics Inc., 1996, Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29-30)
  - Unpermitted Discharges in NY Region 7, 1992 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Valley Watch Inc. - Correspondence and Notes, 1985-1987 (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - "Water Classification Under the Clean Water Act" by Samuel Sage and Aaron Roblan, Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Water Quality Criteria and Safe Drinking Water, 1986-1991; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Water Resources, New York, 1981; 1987; Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Water Resources, Long Island, 1981; Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Washington EPCRA, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Washington Solid Waste Advisory Committee, Subcommittee on Ash Management, 1987-1988 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Wet Cleaning, 1993; 1995-1996 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Wetlands, Training Course Packets and Natural Resource Foundation, 1984; 1988; Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - "What You Should Know and What You Can Do Through the Emergency Planning and Community Right-to-Know Act", 1993 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - "Where did EPCRA Come From?", Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin's New Open Records Laws, 1982; Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Workshop on Spent Pickle Liquor - Advance Materials, 1996 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Workshop on Spent Pickle Liquor - Follow-up Materials, 1996 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Workshop on Spent Pickle Liquor - Proceedings and Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 12 (3-Subject Files), Folder 0)
- Affiliate Associations, 1972-1996; 4; 1.6 cu. ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains correspondence and court documents related to environmental legal action cases pursued by Atlantic States Legal Foundation affiliates and like-minded organizations. These include the Sierra Club, Natural Resources Defence Council, Friends of the Earth and New Jersey Public Interest Research Group. Each file contains multiple cases.
  - Cases, 1972; 1978-1980 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 1)
  - Cases, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 2-3)
  - Cases, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 4-7)
  - Cases, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 8-9)
  - Cases, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 10-12)
  - Cases, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 13-15)
  - Cases, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 16-17)
  - Cases, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 1-2)
  - Cases, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 3-4)
  - Cases, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 5)
  - Cases, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 6-7)
  - Cases, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 1)
  - Cases, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 2)
  - Cases, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 3)
  - Cases, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Affiliate Associations), Folder 4)